Finding Aid for the Medical Artifacts Collection
Eskind Biomedical Library Manuscripts Collection
- Shelf 2 929 DaVinci, Leonardo. Lithographic print, framed, of Leonardo DaVinci. Engraved by J. Postlewhite, ca 1760. Added to inventory May 23, 1995.
- Shelf 2 930 Leeuwenhoek, Anton von. Lithographic print, framed, of Anton von Leeuwenhoek, London, February 26, 1813, by G. Jones. Frame in fair condition. Added to inventory May 23, 1995.
- Shelf 2 931 Rush, Benjamin. “Observations on the Duties of a Physician.” Printed and framed excerpts from a lecture given by Benjamin Rush to the University of Pennsylvania, February 7, 1789. Frame in good condition. Added to inventory May 23, 1995. Donated by Drs. Frist, Scoville, and Kochtitzky.
- Shelf 2 932 White, J. William. Color print, framed, of portrait of J. William White, M.D., 1850-1916, by John Singer Sargent. No. 3 in the Great American Surgeons Series, Ethicon Suture Laboratories, ca 1960. Added to inventory May 23, 1995
- Shelf 2 933 Frazier, Charles Harrison. Color print, framed, of portrait of Charles Harrison Frazier, M.D., 1870-1936, by Frederick Roscher. No. 2 in the Great American Surgeons Series, Ethicon Suture Laboratories, ca 1960. Added to inventory May 23, 1995.
- Shelf 2 934 Agnew, David Hayes. Color print, framed, of portrait of David Hayes Agnew, M.D., 1818-1892, from The Agnew Clinic by Thomas Eakins. No. 4 in the Great American Surgeons Series, Ethicon Suture Laboratories, ca 1960. Added to inventory May 23, 1995.
- Shelf 2 935 Vanderbilt University. Map, framed, of illustrative site plan university center urban renewal area, Vanderbilt, ca 1965. Good condition. Transferred from Vanderbilt School of Medicine, Office of the Dean. Added to inventory May 23, 1995.
- Shelf 3 936 Physick, Philip Syng. Certificate, framed, written in Latin from the Medical Society of Philadelphia, presented to Alexander Bryant. Signed by Dr. Philip Syng Physick (1768-1837), Father of American Surgery. Good condition. Presented to Dr. Barney Brooks by an Appreciative patient, Christmas, 1938. Added to inventory May 23, 1995.
- Shelf 3 937 American College of Physicians. Framed print, signed and numbered (#24), of a sketch of the headquarters of the American College of Physicians by Herbert Pullinyar. Added to inventory May 25, 1995.
- Shelf 3 938 Sargent, John Singer. Framed, print black and white, of John Singer Sargent’s Four Doctors (Osler, Welch, Halsted, and Kelly). Signed in white ink by Dr. Howard A. Kelly. Good condition. Added to inventory May 25, 1995.
- Shelf 4 (Placed on MCN 2) 939 Vanderbilt University. 300th General Hospital Unit. Plaque, wooden shield-shaped, with a small metal plate surrounded by a green painted garland and reading “Service Award of Merit presented to the 300th General Hospital (Vanderbilt Unit) by Peninsular Base Section Mediterranean Theater of Operations.” ca 1945, warped. Added to inventory May 25, 1995.
- Shelf 4 940 Vanderbilt University. 300th General Hospital Unit. Plaque, wooden shield-shaped, with a small metal plate surrounded by a green painted garland and reading “Service Award of Merit presented to the 300th General Hospital (Vanderbilt Unit) by Peninsular Base Section Mediterranean Theater of Operations.” ca 1945, garland is damaged. Added to inventory May 25, 1995.
- Shelf 4 (Placed on MCN 2) 941 Morgan, Hugh Jackson. Framed color print of the portrait The Surgeon General and His Staff by Francis Criss. Signed by Brigadier General Hugh Jackson Morgan. Added to inventory May 25, 1995.
- Shelf 4 (Placed on MCN 2) 942 Vanderbilt University. 300th General Hospital Unit. Framed group photograph of the Medical and Surgical Conference, 300th General Hospital, Naples Italy, January 26-27, 1945. Taken before front entrance of the Ospidali Sanitoria Principi de Piedmonte. Added to inventory May 25, 1995.
- Shelf 4 (Placed on MCN 2) 943 Vanderbilt University. World War I Unit. Framed group photograph of the Vanderbilt Unit, WWI officers and enlisted men. Added to inventory May 25, 1995. Donated by Dr. W. H. Witt.
- Shelf 4 944 Vanderbilt University. 300th General Hospital Unit. Framed certificate. Citation for meritorious service unit plaque presented to the 300th General Hospital Unit. Hand lettered and signed by Brig. Gen. Francis H. Oxx. Added to inventory May 25, 1995.
- Shelf 5 945 Robinson, G. Canby. Framed photograph portrait of G. Canby Robinson Inscribed: “To Al, with best wishes.” Ca. 1927. Added to inventory May 25, 1995.
- Shelf 5 946 Dunn, Ross. Framed photograph portrait of Ross Dunn, Professor of Materia Medica and Therapeutics 1896-99, Vanderbilt University School of Medicine. Added to inventory May 25, 1995.
- Shelf 5 947 Bryan, Worcester Allen. Framed photograph portrait of Worcester Allen Bryan, 1873-1940. Member of Surgical Staff 1900-09, Professor of Principles of Surgery 1909-11, Professor of Surgery and Clinical Surgery 1911-25. Professor of Clinical Surgery 1925-40 Vanderbilt University School of Medicine. Added to inventory May 25, 1995.
- Shelf 5 948 Bigger, J. A. Framed photograph of Dr. J. A. Bigger Inscribed: “Sincerely..,” ca 1930. Added to inventory May 25, 1995.
- Shelf 5 949 Morgan, Hugh Jackson. Framed photograph portrait of Dr. Hugh Jackson Morgan, ca 1930. Added to inventory May 25, 1995.
- Shelf 5 950 Burwell, C. Sidney. Framed photograph portrait of Dr. C. Sidney Burwell Inscribed: “To Alfred Blalock,” ca 1935. Added to inventory May 25, 1995.
- Shelf 5 951 Goodpasture, Ernest W. Framed photograph portrait of Dr. Ernest W. Goodpasture, ca 1940. Added to inventory May 25, 1995.
- Shelf 5 952 Levy, Sanford E. Framed photograph portrait of Dr. Sanford E. Levy. Inscribed: “To Alfred Blalock with warm respect..” ca 1935. Added to inventory May 25, 1995.
- Shelf 5 953 Parker, Edward. Framed photograph portrait of Dr. Edward Parker. Inscribed: “To Dr. Blalock with the highest admiration and esteem..,” ca 1935. Added to inventory May 25, 1995.
- Shelf 5 954 Meleney, Ed. Framed photograph portrait of Dr. Ed Meleney. Inscribed: “To Alfred Blalock with affectionate regards..,” ca 1935. Added to inventory May 25, 1995.
- Shelf 5 955 Pilcher, Cobb. Framed photograph portrait of Dr. Cobb Pilcher, ca 1935 Added to inventory May 25, 1995.
- Shelf 6 956 Ehrenberg G. Framed lithographic print of Dr. G. Ehrenberg, Prof. Berlin. S.W. Leonard, lithographer, ca. 1850, glass broken. Added to inventory May 25, 1995.
- Shelf 6 957 Welch, William H. Framed print of a sketch of Dr William H. Welch, Issued in 1930 by the William H. Welch Medical Library. Frame loose. Added to inventory May 25, 1995.
- Shelf 6 958 Haller, Albert de. Framed lithographic print of Albert de Haller. Lithograph by Grégorie et Deneux, Paris. Ca 1780. Added to inventory May 25, 1995.
- Shelf 6 959 Sydenham, Thomas. Framed engraving of Thomas Sydenham, M.D. London: engraved for Harrison’s edition of Rapin. In the possession of John Sydenham, Esq. Published August 27, 1785. Frame loose. Added to inventory May 25, 1995.
- Shelf 6 960 Hart, Edwin Bret. Framed print of a portrait of Edwin Bret Hart. From a portrait in the Library of Biochemistry at Wisconsin. Frame loose. Donated by E. Neige Todhunter. Added to inventory May 25, 1995.
- Shelf 6 961 Welch, William H. Framed print of a portrait of William H. Welch by Max Brödel. Possibly signed by Welch. Added to inventory May 25, 1995
- Shelf 6 962 Bacon, Roger. Framed Lithographic print of Roger Bacon, ca 1790. Added to inventory May 25, 1995.
- Shelf 6 963 Boerhaave, Herman. Framed engraving of Herman Boerhaave, M.D. Published by E. Bent September 30, 1788. Added to inventory May 25, 1995.
- Shelf 6 964 Hurd, Henry M. Framed photograph of Dr. Henry M. Hurd, first superintendent of Johns Hopkins Hospital. Photographed at Janvier Studios in Baltimore, 1916. Added to inventory May 25, 1995.
- Shelf 6 965 Cruikshank, William. Framed engraving of William Cruikshank. Engraved by J. Corner, published by J. Sewell Cornhill, 1787. Frame loose. Added to inventory May 25, 1995.
- Shelf 6 966 Hippocrates. Framed Oath of Hippocrates, from The Genuine Works of Hippocrates. Translated from the Greek by Francis Adams, Volume 2, London, 1849. Reprinted by Northwestern University Medical School, 1938. Added to inventory May 25, 1995.
- Shelf 6 967 Jenner, Edward. Framed lithographic print of Edward Jenner, M.D. R. M. Meadows sculptor. Ca 1800. Added to inventory May 25, 1995.
- Shelf 7 968 Curie, Pierre and Marie Sklowska. Framed color print illustration of Pierre Curie and Marie Sklodowska Curie by “J.M.P.” Glass broken. Donated by Dr. E. Neige Todhunter. Added to inventory May 26, 1995.
- Shelf 7 969 Pasteur, Louis. Framed color print illustration of Louis Pasteur by “.T.” Donated by E. Neige Todhunter. Added to inventory May 26, 1995.
- Shelf 7 970 Rutherford, Lord. Framed print of a pencil sketch of Lord Rutherford, O.M., F. R. S., by Eugene Montgomery. Note: this artifact number was formerly #386. Donated by E. Neige Todhunter, June 1987. Added to inventory May 26, 1995.
- Shelf 7 971 Curie, Marie Sklowska. Framed print of a charcoal drawing of Marie Curie, by Eugene Montgomery. Donated by E. Neige Todhunter, (June 1987?). Added to inventory May 26, 1995.
- Shelf 7 972 Lind, James. Framed print of the painting James Lind -- Conqueror of Scurvy by Robert Thom from A History of Medicine in Pictures Series, by Parke, Davis & Company, 1959. No glass. Added to inventory May 26, 1995.
- Shelf 8 973 Mendeléff Dimitri Ivanovitsch. Framed portrait with biographical description of Dimitri Ivanovitsch Mendléff (1834-1907). Donated by Dr. E. Neige Todhunter (from the Department of Biochemistry), May 7, 1979. Added to inventory May 26, 1995. Transferred from Vanderbilt Department of Biochemistry.
- Shelf 8 974 Grignard, Victor. Framed portrait with biographical description of Victor Grignard (1871-1935). Donated by Dr. E. Neige Todhunter (from the Department of Biochemistry), May 7, 1979. Added to inventory May 26, 1995. Transferred from Vanderbilt Department of Biochemistry.
- Shelf 8 975 Riddle, Oscar. Framed portrait with biographical description of Dr. Oscar Riddle. From the Armour Laboratories series. Donated by Dr. E. Neige Todhunter (from Dr. Frank Blood in the Department of Biochemistry), May 7, 1979. Added to inventory May 26, 1995. Transferred from Vanderbilt Department of Biochemistry.
- Shelf 8 976 Baumann, Eugen. Framed portrait with biographical description of Dr. Eugen Baumann (1846-1896). Donated by Dr. E. Neige Todhunter (from Dr. Frank Blood in the Department of Biochemistry), May 7, 1979. Added to inventory May 26, 1995. Transferred from Vanderbilt Department of Biochemistry.
- Shelf 8 977 Wöhler, Friedrich. Framed portrait with biographical description of Dr. Friedrich Wöhler (1800-1882). Donated by Dr. E. Neige Todhunter (from the Department of Biochemistry), May 7, 1979. Added to inventory May 26, 1995. Transferred from Vanderbilt Department of Biochemistry.
- Shelf 8 978 Takaki, Baron Kanehiro. Framed portrait with biographical description of Baron Kanehiro Takaki (1849-1920). Donated by Dr. E. Neige Todhunter (from the Department of Biochemistry), May 7, 1979. Added to inventory May 26, 1995. Transferred from Vanderbilt Department of Biochemistry.
- Shelf 8 979 Hopkins F. Gowland. Framed portrait with biographical description of F. Gowland Hopkins (1861-1947). Donated by Dr. E. Neige Todhunter (from the Department of Biochemistry), May 7, 1979. Added to inventory May 26, 1995. Transferred from Vanderbilt Department of Biochemistry.
- Shelf 8 980 Molder, Gerrit Jan. Framed portrait with biographical description of Gerrit Jan Molder (1802-1880). Donated by Dr. E. Neige Todhunter (from the Department of Biochemistry), May 7, 1979. Added to inventory May 26, 1995. Transferred from Vanderbilt Department of Biochemistry.
- Shelf 8 981 Pettenkofer, Max. Framed portrait with biographical description of Max Pettenkofer (1818-1901). Donated by Dr. E. Neige Todhunter (from the Department of Biochemistry), May 7, 1979. Added to inventory May 26, 1995. Transferred from Vanderbilt Department of Biochemistry.
- Shelf 8 982 Vigneaud, Vincent du. Framed portrait with biographical description of Vincent du Vigneaud. Donated by Dr. E. Neige Todhunter (from the Department of Biochemistry), May 7, 1979. Added to inventory May 26, 1995. Transferred from Vanderbilt Department of Biochemistry.
- Shelf 8 983 Boussingault, Jean B. Framed portrait with biographical description of Jean B. Boussingault (1802-1887). Donated by Dr. E. Neige Todhunter (from the Department of Biochemistry), May 7, 1979. Added to inventory May 26, 1995. Transferred from Vanderbilt Department of Biochemistry.
- Shelf 8 984 Rose, Mary Swartz. Framed and signed portrait of Mary Swartz Rose Donated by Dr. E. Neige Todhunter (from the Department of Biochemistry), May 7, 1979. Added to inventory May 26, 1995. Transferred from Vanderbilt Department of Biochemistry.
- Shelf 8 985 Sherman, Henry C. Framed and signed portrait of Dr. Henry C. Sherman. Donated by Dr. E. Neige Todhunter (from the Department of Biochemistry), May 7, 1979. Added to inventory May 26, 1995. Transferred from Vanderbilt Department of Biochemistry.
- Shelf 8 986 Curie, Marie Sklowska. Framed portrait with biographical description of Marie Sklowska Curie (1867-1934). Donated by Dr. E. Neige Todhunter (from the Department of Biochemistry), May 7, 1979. Added to inventory May 26, 1995. Transferred from Vanderbilt Department of Biochemistry.
- Shelf 8 987 Nernst, Walther. Framed portrait with biographical description of Walther Nernst (1864-1941). Donated by Dr. E. Neige Todhunter (from the Department of Biochemistry), May 7, 1979. Added to inventory May 26, 1995. Transferred from Vanderbilt Department of Biochemistry.
- Shelf 8 988 Langmuir, Irving. Framed portrait with biographical description of Irving Langmuir (1881-1957) Donated by Dr. E. Neige Todhunter (from the Department of Biochemistry), May 7, 1979. Added to inventory May 26, 1995. Transferred from Vanderbilt Department of Biochemistry.
- Shelf 8 989 Aston, Francis William. Framed portrait with biographical description of Francis William Aston (1877- ) Donated by Dr. E. Neige Todhunter (from the Department of Biochemistry), May 7, 1979. Added to inventory May 26, 1995. Transferred from Vanderbilt Department of Biochemistry.
- Shelf 8 990 Gibbs, Josiah Williard. Framed portrait with biographical description of Josiah Willard Gibbs (1839-1903). Donated by Dr. E. Neige Todhunter (from the Department of Biochemistry), May 7, 1979. Added to inventory May 26, 1995. Transferred from Vanderbilt Department of Biochemistry.
- Shelf 8 991 Ostwald, Wilhelm. Framed portrait with biographical description of Wilhelm Ostwald (1853-1932). Donated by Dr. E. Neige Todhunter (from the Department of Biochemistry), May 7, 1979. Added to inventory May 26, 1995. Transferred from Vanderbilt Department of Biochemistry.
- Shelf 8 992 Cushing, Harvey W. Framed portrait with biographical description of Harvey W. Cushing (1869-1939) From Armour Laboratory Series. Donated by Dr. E. Neige Todhunter (from Dr. Frank Blood in the Department of Biochemistry), May 7, 1979. Added to inventory May 26, 1995. Transferred from Vanderbilt Department of Biochemistry.
- Shelf 8 993 Abel, John Jacob. Framed portrait with biographical description of Dr. John Jacob Abel (1857-1938). From the Armour Laboratory Series. Donated by Dr. E. Neige Todhunter (from Dr. Frank Blood in the Department of Biochemistry), May 7, 1979. Added to inventory May 26, 1995. Transferred from Vanderbilt Department of Biochemistry.
- Shelf 8 994 Le Chatelier, Henri Louis Framed portrait with biographical description of Henri Louis Le Chatelier (1850-1936). Donated by Dr. E. Neige Todhunter (from the Department of Biochemistry), May 7, 1979. Added to inventory May 26, 1995. Transferred from Vanderbilt Department of Biochemistry.
- Shelf 8 995 Bunsen, Robert Wilhelm. Framed portrait with biographical description of Robert Wilhelm Bunsen (1811-1899). Donated by Dr. E. Neige Todhunter (from the Department of Biochemistry), May 7, 1979. Added to inventory May 26, 1995. Transferred from Vanderbilt Department of Biochemistry.
- Shelf 8 996 Minot, George R. Framed portrait with biographical description of Dr. George R. Minot (1885-1950) From the Armour Laboratories Series. Donated by Dr. E. Neige Todhunter (from Dr. Frank Blood in the Department of Biochemistry), May 7, 1979. Added to inventory May 26, 1995. Transferred from Vanderbilt Department of Biochemistry.
- Shelf 8 997 Doisy, Edward A. Framed portrait with biographical description of Dr. Edward A. Doisy (1893-1986). From the Armour Laboratories Series. Donated by Dr. E. Neige Todhunter (from Dr. Frank Blood in the Department of Biochemistry), May 7, 1979. Added to inventory May 26, 1995. Transferred from Vanderbilt Department of Biochemistry.
- Shelf 8 998 Crafts, James Mason. Framed portrait with biographical description of James Mason Crafts (1839-1917) Donated by Dr. E. Neige Todhunter (from the Department of Biochemistry), May 7, 1979. Added to inventory May 26, 1995. Transferred from Vanderbilt Department of Biochemistry.
- Shelf 8 999 Von Leibig, Justus. Framed portrait with biographical description of Justus Von Liebig (1803-1873). Donated by Dr. E. Neige Todhunter (from the Department of Biochemistry), May 7, 1979. Added to inventory May 26, 1995. Transferred from Vanderbilt Department of Biochemistry.
- Shelf 9 1000 Poll, Heinrich. Framed photograph of Dr. Heinrich Poll, Flexner Lecturer in 1928. Autographed. Added to inventory May 31, 1995.
- Shelf 9 1001 Hardy, Sir William B. Framed photograph of Sir William B. Hardy, Flexner Lecturer in 1931. Autographed. Added to inventory May 31, 1995.
- Shelf 9 1002 Fraser, Francis R. Framed photograph of Dr. Francis R. Fraser, Flexner Lecturer in 1933. Autographed. Added to inventory May 31, 1995.
- Shelf 9 1003 Nystrom, Erik Gunnar. Framed photograph of Erik Gunnar Nystrom, Flexner Lecturer in 1935. Autographed. Added to inventory May 31, 1995.
- Shelf 9 1004 Madsen, Thorvald. Framed photograph of Thorvald Madsen, Flexner Lecturer in 1937 Autographed. Added to inventory May 31, 1995.
- Shelf 9 1005 Györgyi, Albert Szent. Framed photograph of Albert Szent Györgyi, Flexner Lecturer in 1939. Autographed. Added to inventory May 31, 1995.
- Shelf 9 1006 Mellanby, Sir Edward. Framed photograph of Sir Edward Mellanby, Flexner Lecturer in 1947. Autographed. Added to inventory May 31, 1995.
- Shelf 9 1007 Wallgren, Arvid. Framed photograph of Dr. Arvid Wallgren. Flexner Lecturer in 1949. Autographed. Added to inventory May 31, 1995.
- Shelf 9 1008 Kottmeier, Hans Framed photograph of Dr. Hans Kottmeier, Flexner Lecturer in 1951. Autographed. Added to inventory May 31, 1995.
- Shelf 9 1009 Hoffer, Willi. Framed photograph of Willi Hoffer, Flexner Lecturer in 1954. Added to inventory May 31, 1995.
- Shelf 9 1010 Burn, J. Harold. Framed photograph of J. Harold Burn, Flexner Lecturer in 1956. Autographed. Added to inventory May 31, 1995.
- Shelf 9 1011 Burnet, Sir MacFarlane. Framed photograph of Sir MacFarlane Burnet, Flexner Lecturer in 1958. Added to inventory May 31, 1995.
- Shelf 9 1012 Waldenström, Jan G. Framed photograph of Jan G. Waldenström, Flexner Lecturer in 1965. Autographed. Added to inventory May 31, 1995.
- Shelf 9 1013 Young, J. Z. Framed photograph of J. Z. Young, Flexner Lecturer in 1968. Added to inventory May 31, 1995.
- Shelf 9 1014 Gross, Franz. Framed photograph of Franz Gross, Flexner Lecturer in 1970. Autographed. Added to inventory May 31, 1995.
- Shelf 9 1015 Sandblom, Philip. Framed photograph of Philip Sandblom, Flexner Lecturer in 1971. Autographed. Added to inventory May 31, 1995.
- Shelf 9 1016 Burton-Bradley, Burton G. Framed photograph of Burton G. Burton-Bradley, Flexner Lecturer in 1973. Added to inventory May 31, 1995.
- Vanderbilt Files, Series 3: Subject Files 1017 Klein, George. Photograph of George Klein, Flexner Lecturer in 1974. Note: This item was placed in the files located in Historical Collections room 311-A, because the picture is unframed. Added to inventory May 31, 1995.
- Shelf 10 1018 Mackenzie, Sir James. Framed photographic reproduction of a picture of Sir James Mackenzie (1853-1925) and the title page of his book entitled: The Study of the Pulse (London, 1902). Added to inventory May 31, 1995.
- Shelf 10 1019 Harvey, William. Framed photographic reproduction of a picture of William Harvey (1578-1657) and the title page of his book entitled: Execitatio Anatomica de Moto Cordis et Sanguinis in Animalibus (Frankfort, 1628). Added to inventory May 31, 1995.
- Shelf 10 1020 Heberden, William Framed photographic reproduction of a picture of William Heberden (1710-1801) and a description of angina pectoris pages (152-53) from his book entitled: Some Account of a Disorder in the Heart (London, 1768). Added to inventory May 31, 1995.
- Shelf 10 1021 Morgagni, Giovanni Battista. Framed photographic reproduction of a picture of Giovanni Battista Morgagni (1682-1771) and the title page of his book entitled: The Seats and Causes of Disease (London, 1769). Added to inventory May 31, 1995.
- Shelf 10 1022 Auenbrugger, Leopold. Framed photographic reproduction of a picture of Leopold Auenbrugger (1722-1809) and the title page of his book entitled: Inventum Novum ex Percussione Thoracis Humani ut Signo Abstrusos Interni Pectoris Morbos Detegendi (Vindobonae, 1761). Added to inventory June 8, 1995.
- Shelf 10 1023 Peabody, Francis Weld. Framed photographic reproduction of a picture of Francis Weld Peabody (1881- 1927) and the title page of his article entitled: “Clinical Studies of the Respiration, IV. The Vital Capacity of the Lungs and its Relation to Dyspnea,” Archives of Internal Medicine, vol. 20, 1917. Added to inventory June 8, 1995.
- Shelf 10 1024 Hope, James. Framed photographic reproduction of a picture of James Hope (1801-1841) and the title page of his book entitled: A Treatise on the Diseases of the Heart and Great Vessels (Philadelphia, 1846). Added to inventory June 8, 1995.
- Shelf 10 1025 Cabot, Richard Clarke. Framed photographic reproduction of a picture of Richard Clarke Cabot (1868-1939) and the title page of his article entitled: “The Four Common Types of Heart Disease,” Journal of the American Medical Association, vol. 63 p. 1461, 1914. Added to inventory June 8, 1995.
- Shelf 10 1026 Withering, William. Framed photographic reproduction of a picture of William Withering (1741-1799) and the title page of his book entitled: An Account of the Foxglove and Some of its Medical Uses: With Practical Remarks on Dropsy and Other Diseases (Birmingham, 1785) Added to inventory June 8, 1995.
- Shelf 10 1027 Corvisart, Jean-Nicholas. Framed photographic reproduction of a picture of Jean-Nicholas Corvisart (1755-1821) and the title page of his book entitled: Essai sur les Maladies et les Lesions Organiques du Coeur et des Gros Vaisseaux (Third Edition, Paris 1818). Added to inventory June 8, 1995.
- Shelf 10 1028 Starling, Ernest Henry. Framed photographic reproduction of a picture of Ernest Henry Starling (1866-1927) and the title page of his article entitled: “The Regulation of the Heartbeat,” Journal of Physiology, vol. 48 p. 465, 1914. Frame is loose. Added to inventory June 8, 1995.
- Shelf 10 1029 Hales, Stephen. Framed photographic reproduction of a picture of Stephen Hales (1667-1761) and the title page of his book entitled: Statical Essays Containing Hæmastaticks.. (London, 1753). Added to inventory June 8, 1995.
- Shelf 10 1030 Stokes, William. Framed photographic reproduction of a picture of William Stokes (1804-1878) and the title page of his book entitled: The Diseases of the Heart and Aorta (Philadelphia, 1854). Added to inventory June 8, 1995.